ABOUT ME

Confident and reliable IT support engineer with extensive practical experience of working with computers and resolving any support issues that are raised to the service desk. Possessing a proven ability to administer and control the operation, configuration and maintenance of computer based information systems, as well as having an eye for detail and able to multi-task under pressure. Obtaining a powerful knowledge on Linux OS and Command Line, and above all I work as a Front-end Web Developer.

EXPERIENCE

Support Engineer | ICapital AD, UAE - Mar2010 - Oct2014

- Support Engineer on MOH System (Ministry of Health Cerner)
- Maintenance Support
- Installing PC and Imaging
- Hardware Installation and Configuration

IT support technician | Al Qusaily Building AD, UAE - Dec2014 – Oct2020

- Install authorized software to laptops and desktops
- Providing Maintenance Support and break-fix solutions

Volunteer

Front-end Web Developer | Turkey, Istanbul – Jan2021 – till date

building a Progressive Websites voluntarily see it on my website: mohanadlinux.w3spaces.com

SKILLS

Operating Systems: Windows, Linux

Systems: Cerner (health care system), Oracle Database 10g

Networking: Network+

Programming: HTML & CSS & JS, Python, SQL Assistant skills: Git, GitHub, Maintenance (+A)

Key skills: MS Office, LibreOffice

MOHANAD AL SAMANEH



CONTACT INFO



+905388774060





mohanadlinux.w3spaces.com



Aug.30.1983



💍 Single

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics & computer science from Ovidius University, Constanta, Romania - 2008

Oracle Database 10g

from Oracle University KIC, AD, UAE - 2009

LANGUAGES

Arabic, English & Romanian